resume-resource.com 2017-11-22

# Resume-Resource.com Privacy Policy

updated 3/1/2014

## Who We Are

Resume-Resource.com is owned by Sourceline Media, Inc. When we say “we,” “us,” “Resume-Resource.com,” and “Resume Resource,” we are referring to Sourceline Media, Inc. dba Resume-Resource.com a State of Illinois Corporation.  When we say “you,” “customer,” “subscriber,” “visitor,” or “member we are referring to the person or entity that has signed up for our newsletter or purchased one of our products.

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining what we do with any information collected. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## Information We Collect:

**Personal Information**

We collect names and emails for our newsletter subscribers.  If you purchase one of our products then  will collect your credit card information, name, address, email and phone number.

**Log Files**

Like most other Web sites, Resume-Resource.com uses log files to learn about our visitors. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, geographic location, clicks, page views. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track use behavior, block threats, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies**

Resume-Resource.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Resume-Resource.com.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.resume-resource.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Clickbank
  * Chitika
  * Kontera
  * Live Career
  * Tribal Fusion
  * Education Dynamics
  * Lijit Networks
  * Komoona
  * Ontraport

**Pixel Tracking**

Resume-Resource.com or our third party advertising partners may engage in pixel tracking, which is a widely used technique that helps track user activity on a site for the purposes of improving advertisements. A pixel tag is a small pixel with software code that is not visible to the user but helps track user activity. Some of our pages may include pixel tracking for the purposes of re-targeting advertisements to the same user.  If you visit our website then visit other sites that include our advertising partners ads, they may choose to show re-targeted ads.

**Other Third Party Advertisers**

These third party networks, ad partners, ad servers or ad networks may use technology within their advertisements and links that appear on Resume-Resource.com, which may be sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, Pixel Targeting, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Resume-Resource.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Resume-resource.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found by contacting the browser company or looking in their help section.

## How We Use Information

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

We use your name and email address for the sole purpose of sending email information, product offerings and services related to resume writing, cover letter writing, job search and careers.

With the exception of the credit card information, we store the information from your order form to allow us to track issues, find orders and assist customer service.   We do not sell or exchange your personal information.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

You can request removal from our newsletter by hitting the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every newsletter.

## About Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access we keep information on a secure server and use third party mail programs to administer our newsletter.

All areas of the collect information use an https:// URL with SSL security by Trustwave.

## About Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## How To Contact Resume-Resource.com

Visit our [Contact Us ](http://www.resume-resource.com/us-contact-us/) page for information on how to reach us.
